prestigio.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy policy

This policy applies to information that may be collected on the Prestigio site. **By registering on[www.Prestigio.com](http://www.prestigio.com/), you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy and provide us with sincere and true information as it concerns you.**

Prestigio knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. Prestigio is committed to observing and respecting your wishes regarding the information we collect about you on our web site.

## Personal Information

The information we learn from you helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at www.Prestigio.com.

Your transaction history and the information you provide us online on [www.Prestigio.com](http://www.prestigio.com/), by phone or email is securely stored in our customer database and may be provided only to our related companies or certain third parties that we have screened carefully for reliability and integrity.

Prestigio as well as other third parties serving your order may provide you with information related to registration and payment of your order, including advertising, informational and other messages to email address and / or phone number specified by you.

Prestigio is entitled to process your personal data (including, but not limited to, name, last name, phone number) and send it to the specified above third parties in order to fulfill its obligations under your order.

Some of the information we receive from you is voluntary, while much of it is required in order to fulfill your order properly. Failure to provide such information may result in the cancellation of your order. In addition to fulfilling your orders, we use the information that you provide for purposes such as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.

Any personal information you reveal to us is protected. Prestigio maintains security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information to prevent unauthorized removal or alteration of data. Prestigio meets accepted standards of security for all transactions that may involve payment of fees through a service available through this site, including the use of encryption and SSL services. Credit card numbers are not stored longer than is required for verification and completion of the subject transaction. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

At any time you may access and rectify all the information that concerns you and stored at Prestigio. You can at any time make a request to Prestigio to find out what personal information we have concerning you, and by request, modify this information. 

## E-mail Policy

Other than the exceptions noted in this Policy, Prestigio will not sell, share or otherwise distribute your e-mail address communicated to us or otherwise collected through the use of this site. Any e-mail address supplied directly to Prestigio with respect to online orders, catalog requests, and requests for other information will remain in the sole possession of Prestigio and its related companies.

**If you do not want to receive promotional e-mails from Prestigio in the future,** please let us know by contacting us by e-mail, or by calling us at the contact telephone numbers.

If you supply us with your postal address you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. **If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please contact us by e-mail or by calling us at the contact telephone numbers.**  

## Cookies

Like most retail web sites, we use "cookies," which are pieces of data given to your browser that allow our web site to identify you when you access our site. While some concern has been expressed over the privacy implications of cookies, it is important for you to understand that cookies cannot extract any information about you that you have not already revealed voluntarily. The vast majority of Internet users now appreciate cookies as a convenience feature for shopping online. If you desire, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

If you have any questions regarding any of the elements of our web privacy policy, please contact us by mail, e-mail or by phone.
